The City of Fayetteville is making a special effort to recognize its bus drivers
ahead of the newly proclaimed Transit Driver Appreciation Day, happening Saturday.
As part of the event, the City is celebrating its longest serving driver on the
force. That driver is Sherry Christian.
As part of the event, the City is its longest serving driver on the force.
That driver is Sherry Christian.
Christian has been a driver for 25 years.
The Fayetteville native believes driving a school bus allows her to give back to her
community. Christian has been a driver for 25 years.
Fayetteville native believes driving a school bus allows her to give back to her
The Fayetteville native believes driving a school bus allows her to give back to her
community. She says that the best part the job is watching the children who ride her
bus grow up.
She says that the best part of the job is watching the children who ride her bus
grow up. She says that the best part of the job is watching the children who ride
her bus grow up.
Driver Appreciation Day has been celebrated across the country as far back as 2009.
Transit Driver Appreciation Day has been celebrated across the country as far back
as 2009. Transit Driver Appreciation Day has been celebrated across the country as
far back as 2009.
However, this week the City of Fayetteville issued a proclamation for the day to
take place March 18th.
However, this week the City of Fayetteville